Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - I-L
        - LaBelle, Patti - The best of Patti LaBelle, 1982; SR-24431; LaBelle, Patti (Box 46)
          Catalog # AL 36997; A-side Matrix # AL 36997-1B
        - LaBelle, Patti - Winner in you, 1986; SR-24432; LaBelle, Patti (Box 46)
          Catalog # MCA-5737; A-side Matrix # MCA 5530-PL-7
        - LaBelle, Patti - Tasty, 1978; SR-24433; LaBelle, Patti (Box 46)
          Catalog # AL 35335; A-side Matrix # AL 35335-1A
        - Ladysmith Black Mambazo - Inala, 1986; SR-24434; Ladysmith Black Mambazo (Box 47)
          Catalog # SERLP 1; A-side Matrix # SERLP-1-A
          Serengeti Records
        - Lake, Oliver - Jump up, 1982; SR-24435; Lake, Oliver (Box 47)
          Catalog # GR-1201; A-side Matrix # GR-1201-A
          Gramavision
        - Lakeside - Fantastic voyage, 1980; SR-24436; Lakeside (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24437. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JD-12130; A-side Matrix # YD-12130-A
        - Lakeside - Fantastic voyage, 1980; SR-24437; Lakeside (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24436. 2 copies.
        - Lakeside - Your wish is my command, 1981; SR-24438; Lakeside (Box 47)
          Catalog # S-26; A-side Matrix # S-26-A-SP
        - Lakeside - Keep on moving straight ahead, 1981; SR-24439; Lakeside (Box 47)
          Catalog # JD-13032; A-side Matrix # YD-13032-A
        - Lane, Suzi - Oh, la, la, 1979; SR-24440; Lane, Suzi (Box 47)
          Catalog # 6E-207; A-side Matrix # 6E-207-A
          Elektra
        - Larrice - Bop 'til I drop, 1984; SR-24441; Larrice (Box 47)
          Catalog # SWRL 2227; A-side Matrix # SWRL-2227-A
          Streetwise
        - Lars B - Unknown substance EP, 1997; SR-24442; Lars B (Box 47)
          Catalog # BLISS 007; A-side Matrix # BLISS 007 A
          Bliss
        - LaRue, D. C. - Ca-the-drals, 1976; SR-24443; LaRue, D. C. (Box 47)
          Catalog # PY-9003; A-side Matrix # PY 9003A K
          Pyramid
        - LaRue, D. C. - Confessions, 1978; SR-24444; LaRue, D. C. (Box 47)
          Catalog # NBLP 7098; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7089-AS-RE-1
        - LaRue, D. C. - Forces of the night, 1979; SR-24445; LaRue, D. C. (Box 47)
          Catalog # NBLP 7160; A-side Matrix # MBLP 7160AS K1
        - Last Poets - Freedom express, 1988; SR-24446; Last Poets (Box 47)
          Catalog # JAZID LP8; A-side Matrix # JAZID 8 LP A1
          Acid Jazz
        - Last Kreep - The good scratching record, 2001; SR-24447; Last Kreep (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24448. 2 copies.
          Catalog # HHS 033; A-side Matrix # SIDE A
          Chip Shop Spam Records
        - Last Kreep - The good scratching record, 2001; SR-24448; Last Kreep (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24447. 2 copies.
        - Latin All Stars - I like it like that, 1997; SR-24449; Latin All Stars (Box 47)
          Catalog # QAL-650; A-side Matrix # QAL-650-A
          Quality Records
          Ontario, Canada
        - Lattisaw, Stacy - With you, 1981; SR-24450; Lattisaw, Stacy (Box 47)
          Catalog # SD 16049; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-814711-C
        - Lattisaw, Stacy - Sneakin' out, 1981; SR-24451; Lattisaw, Stacy (Box 47)
          Catalog # 90002-1; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-8249 75-E
        - Lattisaw, Stacy - Young and in love, 1979; SR-24452; Lattisaw, Stacy (Box 47)
          Catalog # SD 5214; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-794301-A
        - Lattisaw, Stacy - Dynamite!, 1980; SR-24453; Lattisaw, Stacy (Box 47)
          Catalog # DMD 233; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-38329-2
        - Laurence, Paul - Haven't you heard, 1985; SR-24454; Laurence, Paul (Box 47)
          Catalog # ST-12407; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12407-Z1
        - Law, Barbara - Take all of me, 1979; SR-24455; Law, Barbara (Box 47)
          Catalog # AL 36148; A-side Matrix # PAL 36148-1D
          Pavillion
        - Laws, Eloise - Ain't it good feeling good, 1977; SR-24456; Laws, Eloise (Box 47)
          Catalog # AL 34379; A-side Matrix # AL-34379-1A
          Invictus
        - Laws, Ronnie - Mr. Nice guy, 1983; SR-24457; Laws, Ronnie (Box 47)
          Catalog # ST-12261; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12261
        - L.A.X. - Possesed, 1981; SR-24458; L.A.X. (Box 47)
          Catalog # PRL D 609; A-side Matrix # P RLD609AS-1A
        - Lancelot Layne - Neo calypso, 1974; SR-24459; Lancelot Layne (Box 47)
          Catalog # KLS-051; A-side Matrix # KLS 051 A
          Ka La Loo
        - Lazarus - Lazarus, 1977; SR-24460; Lazarus (Box 47)
          Catalog # BKL1-2297; A-side Matrix # BKL-1-2297 A-1
          Midland International
        - LCD - Endor fun, 1996; SR-24461; LCD (Box 47)
          Catalog # CLP 9790-1; A-side Matrix # CLP-9790-1-A
          Hypnotic
        - League of Gentlemen - The League of Gentlemen, 1981; SR-24462; League of Gentlemen; Fripp, Robert (Box 47)
          Catalog # PD-1-6317; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6317-AS-PW-1
        - Ledernacken - Shimmy and shake, 1985; SR-24463; Ledernacken (Box 47)
          Catalog # SBR 8T; A-side Matrix # SBR 8T A1
          Strike Back Records
        - Lee, Byron - Wine miss tiny, 1985; SR-24464; Lee, Byron; Dragonaires (Box 47)
          Catalog # DY3449; A-side Matrix # DY3449-A2
          Dynamic Sounds
        - Lee, Byron - De music hot mama, 1988; SR-24465; Lee, Byron; Dragonaires (Box 47)
          Catalog # DY 3459; A-side Matrix # DY 3459-A
        - Lee, Byron - Soca girl, 1986; SR-24466; Lee, Byron; Dragonaires (Box 47)
          Catalog # DY 3450; A-side Matrix # DY-3450-A
        - Lee, Byron - Jamaica carnival, 1990; SR-24467; Lee, Byron; Dragonaires (Box 47)
          Catalog # DY 3462; A-side Matrix # VP DY 3462-A
        - Lee, Rod - New beginnings part 2 EP, 2002; SR-24468; Lee, Rod; DJ Rod Lee (Box 47)
          Catalog # CKRLNB2-002; A-side Matrix # CKRLNB2-002-A
          Club Kids
        - Lee, Rod - EP volume 1, 2001; SR-24469; Lee, Rod; DJ Rod Lee (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24470. Different discs.
          Catalog # BBR-2001; A-side Matrix # 0011X15A
        - Lee, Rod - Creep tonight project, 2002; SR-24470; Lee, Rod; DJ Rod Lee (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24469. Different discs.
          Catalog # CBR-CK/010; A-side Matrix # 0202X15-A
        - Lee, Rod - Shut em down EP, 2003; SR-24471; Lee, Rod; DJ Rod Lee (Box 47)
          Catalog # CTX-9; A-side Matrix # MCR-RCE
          Club Trax Records
        - Leer, Thomas - Letter from America (disc one), 1982; SR-24472; Leer, Thomas (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24473. Double album.
          Catalog # A RIPE 1; A-side Matrix # A-RIPE-1-A
          Cachalot Records
        - Leer, Thomas - Letter from America (disc two), 1982; SR-24473; Leer, Thomas (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24472. Double album.
          Catalog # A RIPE 1; A-side Matrix # A-RIPE-1-C
        - Lefel, Edith - La kle, 1988; SR-24474; Lefel, Edith (Box 47)
          Catalog # GD 43; A-side Matrix # GD043A10
        - Leftfield - Release the pressure (disc two), 1995; SR-24475; Leftfield (Box 47)
          Catalog # HAND29TP; A-side Matrix # HAND 29 TPX-C2
        - Leftfield - Release the pressure (disc one), 1995; SR-24476; Leftfield (Box 47)
          Catalog # HAND29TP; A-side Matrix # HAND 29 TPX-A2
        - Leftfield - Release the pressure, 1995; SR-24477; Leftfield (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24478. 2 copies.
          Catalog # HAND29T; A-side Matrix # HAND 29 T A
        - Leftfield - Release the pressure, 1995; SR-24478; Leftfield (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24477. 2 copies.
        - Leftfield - Dusted, 1999; SR-24479; Leftfield; Roots Manuva (Box 47)
          Catalog # 44 79335; A-side Matrix # XSS-79335-A
        - Leftfield - The afro-left EP, 1995; SR-24480; Leftfield; Djum Djum (Box 47)
          Catalog # HAND23T; A-side Matrix # 01 662116 20 1A1
        - Leisure Process - Love cascade, 1982; SR-24481; Leisure Process (Box 47)
          Catalog # 44-02989; A-side Matrix # XSS 170179-1A
        - Leisure Process - Cashflow, 1983; SR-24482; Leisure Process (Box 47)
          Catalog # 44-03806; A-side Matrix # XSS-170872-1A
        - Lema, Ray - Nangadeef, 1989; SR-24483; Lema, Ray (Box 47)
          Catalog # MLPS 9829; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9829-A
        - LeMans, Tony - Tony LeMans, 1989; SR-24484; LeMans, Tony (Box 47)
          Catalog # 1-25995; A-side Matrix # 1-25995-A
          Paisley Park Records
        - Lemon D - Urban flava part 1, 1995; SR-24485; Lemon D (Box 47)
          Catalog # MET H 014; A-side Matrix # METH014 AA-02-1-1
          Metalheandz
        - Lennon, John - Imagine: John Lennon, music from the motion picture (disc one), 1988; SR-24486; Lennon, John (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24487. Double album.
          Catalog # C1-90803; A-side Matrix # C1-1-90803
        - Lennon, John - Imagine: John Lennon, music from the motion picture (disc two), 1988; SR-24487; Lennon, John (Box 47)
          In same jacket as # SR-24486. Double album.
        - Leslie, Kelly - Leslie, Kelly & John Ford Coley, 1980; SR-24488; Leslie, Kelly; Coley, John Ford (Box 48)
          Catalog # SP-4841; A-side Matrix # A+M SP04841A-P2
        - Letta - Free soul, 1986; SR-24489; Letta (Box 48)
          Catalog # ST-2929; A-side Matrix # STI-2929-A1
        - Levan, Larry - Larry Levan's greatest mixes volume 2 (disc two), 1979; SR-24491; Levan, Larry (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-24491. Double album.
          Catalog # SA 8533; A-side Matrix # SA-8533-CDJ-1
        - Levan, Larry - Larry Levan's greatest mixes volume 2 (disc three), 1979; SR-24492; Levan, Larry (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-24490. Double album.
          Catalog # SA 8533; A-side Matrix # SA-8533-EDJ-1
        - Levi 167 - Something fresh to swing to; The other side, 1987; SR-24493; Levi 167 (Box 48)
          Catalog # BB-900; A-side Matrix # BB-900-A
          B-Boy Records
          Bronx, New York
        - Levi, Philip - Mi God-mi king, 1984; SR-24494; Levi, Philip (Box 48)
          Catalog # MLPS 7815; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7815-A
        - Levy, Barrington - Murderer, 1993; SR-24495; Levy, Barrington; Rakim (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-24495. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MCA8P 2728; A-side Matrix # MCA8P-2728-1
        - Levy, Barrington - Murderer, 1993; SR-24496; Levy, Barrington; Rakim (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-24494. 2 copies.
        - Lewis, Huey - Picture this, 1982; SR-24497; Lewis, Huey; News (Box 48)
          Catalog # CHR 1340; A-side Matrix # CHR-1340-A5
        - Lewis, Joey - Calypso disco, 1976; SR-24498; Lewis, Joey; His Orchestra (Box 48)
          Catalog # KDS-2009; A-side Matrix # KDS-2009-S1
          Kalinda
          Canada
        - Lewis, Ramsey - Legacy, 1978; SR-24499; Lewis, Ramsey (Box 48)
          Catalog # AL 35483; A-side Matrix # PAL-35483-2C
        - Leyden Zar - Leyden Zar, 1981; SR-24500; Leyden Zar (Box 48)
          Catalog # SP-4860; A-side Matrix # SP-04860-AS-CP2
        - LHB - The pleutonique EP, 1996; SR-25501; LHB (Box 48)
          Catalog # BLST 5; A-side Matrix # BLST 5 A1
          Bolshi Records
        - Liaisons Dangereuses - Liaisons Dangereuses, 1981; SR-25502; Liaisons Dangereuses (Box 48)
          Catalog # CHBB-MUSIC; A-side Matrix # 99S2-A
          Roadrunner Records
        - Lievaux, Jean-Yves - Transformances, 1982; SR-25503; Lievaux, Jean-Yves (Box 48)
          Catalog # 310 122; A-side Matrix # 310 122 A
          Trema
        - Lighthouse Family - High, 1997; SR-25504; Lighthouse Family (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25505. 2 copies.
          Catalog # HIGH 2; A-side Matrix # HIGH 2 A
        - Lighthouse Family - High, 1997; SR-25505; Lighthouse Family (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25504. 2 copies.
        - Lil Suzy - Turn the beat around, 1994; SR-25506; Lil Suzy; Garcia, Tony (Box 48)
          Catalog # WAR-150; A-side Matrix # WAR-150-A
        - Lipps, Inc - The gossip song; How long, 1980; SR-25507; Lipps, Inc (Box 48)
          Catalog # NBD 20230; A-side Matrix # NBD-20230-DJ-AS
        - Lipps, Inc - Designer music, 1981; SR-25508; Lipps, Inc (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25509. Different discs.
          Catalog # NBLP 7262; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7262-AS-PW
        - Lipps, Inc - Hold me down, 1981; SR-25509; Lipps, Inc (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25508. Different discs.
          Catalog # NBD 20238; A-side Matrix # NBD-20238-81-CS-201 PW-2
        - Lipps, Inc - Pucker up, 1980; SR-25510; Lipps, Inc (Box 48)
          Catalog # NBLP 7242; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7242-AS
        - Lipps, Inc - Mouth to mouth, 1979; SR-25511; Lipps, Inc (Box 48)
          Catalog # NBLP 7197; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7197-AS
        - Liquid Gold - Liquid Gold, 1979; SR-25512; Liquid Gold (Box 48)
          Catalog # RRLP 9017; A-side Matrix # RRLP-9017-AS-KL2
          Parachute
        - Liquid Liquid - Successive reflexes, 1981; SR-25513; Liquid Liquid (Box 48)
          Catalog # 99-09; A-side Matrix # 99-09-EP-A
          99 Records
        - Lisa Lisa - Lisa Lisa & Cult Jam with Full Force, 1985; SR-25514; Lisa Lisa; Cult Jam; Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam; Full Force (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25515. Different discs.
          Catalog # BFC 40135; A-side Matrix # AL 40135-1B
        - Full Force - Temporary love thing, 1986; SR-25515; Full Force (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25514. Different discs.
          Catalog # 44-05912; A-side Matrix # XSS-175184-1A
        - Lisa Lisa - Spanish fly, 1987; SR-25516; Lisa Lisa; Cult Jam; Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam (Box 48)
          Catalog # AL 40477; A-side Matrix # AL-40477-1B G1
        - Little Beaver - Party down, 1974; SR-25517; Little Beaver (Box 48)
          Catalog # LP-2604; A-side Matrix # CAT-2604-A
          Cat
        - Little Harry - Dj clash volume 2, 1983; SR-25518; Little Harry; Billy Boyo (Box 48)
          Catalog # GREL 50; A-side Matrix # GREL 50 A
          Greensleeves Records
        - Live - Strut your stuff, 1981; SR-25519; Live (Box 48)
          Catalog # TS-2006; A-side Matrix # TS-2006-A
          The Sound of Brooklyn
        - L.L. Cool J - Bigger and deffer, 1987; SR-25520; L.L. Cool J (Box 48)
          Catalog # 450515 1; A-side Matrix # 450515-1 A1
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Lloyd-D-Stiff - Punnany come through, 1995; SR-25521; Lloyd-D-Stiff; Zarro (Box 48)
          Catalog # WAR 001; A-side Matrix # WAR001 A
          Warrior Productions
        - Lloyd-D-Stiff - Skin to skin, 1988; SR-25522; Lloyd-D-Stiff (Box 48)
          Catalog # GALP-003; A-side Matrix # GALP-003-A
          Gyasi
        - Lloyd-D-Stiff - Informer fi dead, 1995; SR-25523; Lloyd-D-Stiff (Box 48)
          Catalog # WAR 002; A-side Matrix # WAR 002 A
        - Lloyd, Ian - 3WC, 1980; SR-25524; Lloyd, Ian (Box 48)
          Catalog # SB 7110; A-side Matrix # ST-SB-804567-A
          Scotti Brothers
        - Lobo - Caribbean Carnival, 1981; SR-25525; Lobo (Box 48)
          Catalog # DMD 284; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40270-1
        - Logan, Geri - Come and get it, 1980; SR-25526; Logan, Geri (Box 48)
          Catalog # MCA-5298; A-side Matrix # MCA-2909-W1
        - London Funk Allstars - Can ya understand, 1995; SR-25527; London Funk Allstars (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25528. Different discs.
          Catalog # ZEN 1226; A-side Matrix # ZEN-1226-A1
          Ninja Tune
        - Up, Bustle and Out - Aquí no má; The hand of contraband, 1995; SR-25528; Up, Bustle and Out (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25527. Different discs.
          Catalog # ZEN 1228; A-side Matrix # ZEN 1228 A1
        - London Funk Allstars - Can ya understand, 1995; SR-25529; London Funk Allstars (Box 48)
        - London Funk Allstars - Sure shot, 1995; SR-25530; London Funk Allstars (Box 48)
          Catalog # ZEN 1236; A-side Matrix # ZEN 1238 A1
        - London Funk Allstars - London funk volume 1 (disc one), 1995; SR-25084; London Funk Allstars (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25085. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 16; A-side Matrix # ZEN-16 F1
        - London Funk Allstars - London funk volume 1 (disc two), 1995; SR-25085; London Funk Allstars (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25084. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 16; A-side Matrix # ZEN-16 N1
        - Lone - Je représente, 1996; SR-25531; Lone (Box 48)
          Catalog # 2696; A-side Matrix # 2696 A
        - Lone - Tricard, 1995; SR-25532; Lone (Box 48)
          Catalog # 6229; A-side Matrix # LONE 01 A
        - Lonyo - Summer of love, 2000; SR-25533; Lonyo (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25534. 2 copies.
          Catalog # EAS-15732-1; A-side Matrix # 25-EAS-15732-1-A
        - Lonyo - Summer of love, 2000; SR-25534; Lonyo (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25533. 2 copies.
        - Loose Ends - So where are you?, 1985; SR-25535; Loose Ends (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25536. 2 copies.
          Catalog # V2340; A-side Matrix # V 2340 A-4U-1-1
        - Loose Ends - So where are you?, 1985; SR-25536; Loose Ends (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-25535. 2 copies.
        - Lord, CM - You're the only one, 1983; SR-25537; Lord, CM (Box 48)
          Catalog # DL-1217; A-side Matrix # DL-1217-A
          Wave
        - Lord Kossity - Everlord (disc one), 2000; SR-25538; Lord Kossity (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-24539. Double album.
          Catalog # NV 32461; A-side Matrix # NV 3246-1A
          Naive
        - Lord Kossity - Everlord (disc two), 2000; SR-25539; Lord Kossity (Box 48)
          In same jacket as # SR-24538. Double album.
          Catalog # NV 32461; A-side Matrix # NV 3246-C
        - Lord Melody - Sings calypso, 1958; SR-25540; Lord Melody (Box 48)
          Catalog # 906; A-side Matrix # 906A-1
          Cook
        - Lords of the New Church - Open your eyes; Holy war, 1982; SR-25541; Lords of the New Church (Box 48)
          Catalog # SP-70962; A-side Matrix # AM SP 070962-A T1
        - Louis, JJ - Ready or not; Untitled, 2000; SR-25542; Louis, JJ; Sovereign; 2000 Mix (Box 48)
          Catalog # 003; A-side Matrix # N19 003
          N19 Recordings
        - Love & Kisses - You must be love, 1979; SR-25543; Love & Kisses (Box 48)
          Catalog # NBLP 7157; A-side Matrix # NBLP 7157-AS
        - Love De-Luxe - Here comes that sound again, 1978; SR-25544; Love De-Luxe; Hawkshaw's Discophonia (Box 49)
          Catalog # WBSD 8827; A-side Matrix # WBSD-8827-WAA-8846-V11-S-M1
        - Love Machine - The Love Machine, 1978; SR-25545; Love Machine (Box 49)
          Catalog # BDS 5710; A-side Matrix # BDS 5710-1B
        - Love, Tony - We're doing it together; My feelings will never change, 1980; SR-25546; Love, Tony (Box 49)
          Catalog # HSR 105; A-side Matrix # HSR-105-A
          Ham-Sem Records
        - Love Tractor - Love Tractor, 1982; SR-25547; Love Tractor (Box 49)
          Catalog # DB 60; A-side Matrix # DB 60 A
          DB Recs
        - Love Unlimited Orchestra - Music maestro please, 1975; SR-25548; Love Unlimited Orchestra (Box 49)
          Catalog # T-480; A-side Matrix # T1-M-480-AS-2
        - Love Unlimited Orchestra - Welcome aboard, 1981; SR-25549; Love Unlimited Orchestra; Lewis, Webster (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 37425; A-side Matrix # PAL-37425-1C
          Unlimited Gold
        - Love Unlimited Orchestra - Brazilian love song, 1976; SR-25086; Love Unlimited Orchestra (Box 49)
          Catalog # TCD-64; A-side Matrix # M-TCD-64-AS-1C
        - Lovebug Starski - House rocker, 1986; SR-25550; Lovebug Starski (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25551. Different discs.
          Catalog # BFE 40255; A-side Matrix # AL-40255-1C
        - Whistle - Whistle, 1986; SR-25551; Whistle (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25550. Different discs.
          Catalog # SEL 21615; A-side Matrix # SEL-21615-A
        - Loverboy - Keep it up, 1983; SR-25552; Loverboy (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 38703; A-side Matrix # AL-38703-3C
        - Loverde - Iko Iko, 1980; SR-25553; Loverde (Box 49)
          Catalog # PDS 406; A-side Matrix # PDS 406 A
          Prism
        - Lovesmith, Michael - I can make it happen, 1983; SR-25554; Lovesmith, Michael (Box 49)
          Catalog # 6045ML; A-side Matrix # 6045ML-A-15A3LN
        - Lowe, Nick - Nick the knife, 1982; SR-25555; Lowe, Nick (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 37932; A-side Matrix # AL-37932-1C
        - L.T.D. - Devotion, 1979; SR-25556; L.T.D. (Box 49)
          Catalog # SP-4771; A-side Matrix # SP-5279-M3
        - L'Trimm - Grab it!, 1988; SR-25557; L'Trimm (Box 49)
          Catalog # HTLP 3307; A-side Matrix # HTLP 3307-A
          Time-X Records
        - L'Trimm - Cars with the boom, 1988; SR-25558; L'Trimm (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25559. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 1247; A-side Matrix # STDM-56105-1
        - L'Trimm - Cars with the boom, 1988; SR-25559; L'Trimm (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25558. Different discs.
          Catalog # HAL 1284; A-side Matrix # HAL-1284-A-RE-1
        - Lucas, Carrie - Simply Carrie, 1977; SR-25560; Lucas, Carrie (Box 49)
          Catalog # BVL1-2220; A-side Matrix # BVL1-2220-A
          Soul Train
        - Luciano - Life, 1996; SR-25561; Luciano (Box 49)
          Catalog # IJA 2017; A-side Matrix # IJA 2017 A1
          Island Jamaica
        - Lucien, Jon - Premonition, 1976; SR-25562; Lucien, Jon (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 34255; A-side Matrix # PAL 34255-1D
        - Luis, Edward Anthony - Sugaree, 1989; SR-25563; Luis, Edward Anthony (Box 49)
          Catalog # SL 7001; A-side Matrix # SL-7001-A
          Skyyline Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Luke - Lukes booty calls and chants (disc one), 2000; SR-25564; Luke (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25565. Double album.
          Catalog # XR 260-1; A-side Matrix # XR-260-1-A
          Lil' Joe Records
        - Luke - Lukes booty calls and chants (disc two), 2000; SR-25565; Luke (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25564. Double album.
          Catalog # XR 260-1; A-side Matrix # XR-260-1-C
        - Lulu - Lulu, 1981; SR-25566; Lulu (Box 49)
          Catalog # AAB-11006; A-side Matrix # M-11006-AS-P1
          Alfa
        - Lunatic Calm - LC double 'O' series, 1998; SR-25567; Lunatic Calm (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25568. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FABR018T; A-side Matrix # FABR018T-A
          Fused & Bruised
        - Lunatic Calm - LC double 'O' series, 1998; SR-25568; Lunatic Calm (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25567. 2 copies.
        - Luscious Jackson - Nervous breakthrough (disc one), 2000; SR-25569; Luscious Jackson (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25570. Double album.
          Catalog # SPRO 7087 6 15107 13; A-side Matrix # SPRO-15107-A
          Grand Royal
        - Luscious Jackson - Nervous breakthrough (disc two), 2000; SR-25570; Luscious Jackson (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25569. Double album.
          Catalog # SPRO 7087 6 15107 13; A-side Matrix # SPRO-15107-C
        - Lynn, Cheryl - Keep it hot, 1979; SR-25571; Lynn, Cheryl (Box 49)
          Catalog # 43-11261; A-side Matrix # XSS 167187-1A
        - Lynn, Cheryl - In the night, 1981; SR-25572; Lynn, Cheryl (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 37034; A-side Matrix # PAL-37034-2C
        - Lynn, Cheryl - In love, 1979; SR-25573; Lynn, Cheryl (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 36145; A-side Matrix # AL-36145-2B
        - Lynn, Cheryl - Start over, 1987; SR-25574; Lynn, Cheryl (Box 49)
          Catalog # ST-53035; A-side Matrix # B-26589-Z2
          Manhattan Records